One wicket
friend
Oye iss weekend pe you were going to take term insurance
na what happened
Hey I will take it didi comfortably now let me watch the match
Sky is coming kind
of situation I would not worry about
losing the team what happen looks
like
Surya bhai here now bro when you
can postpone such an important work then I will also
comfortably go to play the match
Important work
term insurance
ICICI Prove i Protect Smart Plus
[Music] The sooner you take it the cheaper it will be
and if you have to postpone it then
I will also chill
Still missing the team I will lose the game [Music]
If to be now it will be too late
ICICI [Music]
Prove i Protect Smart Plus don't delay buy now it's a
six
ICICI Particulars with life insurance feel
responsible dear ji